<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>🪴 About Me on</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/</link><description>Recent content in 🪴 About Me on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.brianrahadi.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>University Transfer - Benefits and Tips</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/university-transfer-benefits-and-tips/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 23:08:28 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/university-transfer-benefits-and-tips/</guid><description>Note: This post has the same content from this sfuia blog. I cross-post it as I was the writer and want to provide more content to my personal website.</description></item><item><title>Term Review - Fall 2022</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/term-review-2022fall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 14:23:20 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/term-review-2022fall/</guid><description>Intro Fall 2022 has been quite a rough ride as it&amp;rsquo;s my first time taking 4 CMPT courses. There were some moments where I didn&amp;rsquo;t get the time to revise some content, but overall, this term was pretty good.</description></item><item><title>Term Review - Summer 2022</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/term-review-2022summer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 17:35:44 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/term-review-2022summer/</guid><description>Intro Term Review is an every-4-month journal to share all my thoughts and experiences during the finished term. It acts as both my journal and course review (for those who are planning to take similar courses).</description></item><item><title>Experience</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 22:03:02 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/experience/</guid><description>Education Simon Fraser University (May 2022 - Apr. 2024 Expected) Bachelor of Science, Computing Science in Software Systems Langara College (Sep.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 10:20:08 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/projects/</guid><description>One of the reasons why I liked software is how easy it is to build things with minimal tools (just a laptop and an internet!</description></item><item><title>Langara CS to SFU CS/ SoSy Transfer Guide</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/sfu-cs-transfer-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 14:54:10 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/sfu-cs-transfer-guide/</guid><description>Last Updated: 28 June 2022
Introduction Hello! My name is Brian. I have just transferred to Simon Fraser University&amp;rsquo;s Software Systems program this summer after graduating from Langara with an Associate in Computer Science.</description></item><item><title>Why you should write more ✍(◔◡◔)</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/whywrite/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 20:10:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/whywrite/</guid><description>In my transition period from junior high to high school years, I used to be paid to write. Sounds cool at first, until I told everyone that I am just writing for a game guide.</description></item><item><title>Book Summary - The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/subtleart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 10:39:31 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/subtleart/</guid><description>Self-help advice which tells you to become the person you want to be only reinforces the idea that you are not that thing Pursuing something only reinforces that you lack it in the first place.</description></item><item><title>Book Summary - The Almanack of Naval Ravikant</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/navalmanack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 10:31:18 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/navalmanack/</guid><description>Building Wealth Understand How Wealth Is Created It’s not really about hard work. You can work in a restaurant eighty hours a week, and you’re not going to get rich.</description></item><item><title>Book Summary - Deep Work</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/deepwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 10:20:08 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/deepwork/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The ability to perform deep work is becoming increasingly rare at exactly the same time it is becoming increasingly valuable in our economy.</description></item><item><title>Books</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/books/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 10:20:08 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/books/</guid><description>I enjoy reading books. I have mostly read non-fiction books, but trying to explore other genres as well. Here is a list of books that I would recommend to others:</description></item><item><title>Book Summary - 7 Habits of Highly Effective Teens</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/7habits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 10:15:28 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/7habits/</guid><description>We need a paradigm, paradigm is the way you see something, your point of view. Paradigms need to be principle-centered</description></item><item><title>Book Summary - How to Become a Straight-A Student</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/straightA/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 10:06:57 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/straightA/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The simple truth is that the brute force techniques used by most students are incredibly inefficient.&amp;rdquo; - Cal Newport</description></item><item><title>Book Summary - Atomic Habits</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/atomichabits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 09:33:41 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/atomichabits/</guid><description>”We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence is not an act, but a habit.” - Aristotle
“The costs of your good habits are in the present.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/blog/</guid><description>Some of my writings:
Langara to SFU CS Transfer Guide College Transfer Pros and Cons Summer 2022 Term Review Fall 2022 Term Review</description></item><item><title>Tools</title><link>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.brianrahadi.com/notes/tools/</guid><description>Software TickTick serves as my to-do list x habit tracker x pomodoro timer Learning Obsidian to capture my thoughts Still using [Notion] from time to time mainly for its tables and collaboration features StayFocusd and Forest have helped me to be indistractable one sec and Opal have also helped me tremendously in reducing my phone&amp;rsquo;s social media and screen time consumption Hardware I use the latest MacBook Pro with Intel as my daily driver This Samsung 27-inch monitor is my first external monitor and I have been loving it I type and scroll with Logitech Keyboard and Mouse set.</description></item></channel></rss>